# MARK **MITAU**

+254790398038



mitaumark0@gmail.com



Nairobi, Kenya



# Medical Laboratory Officer

## **SUMMARY**

Highly motivated and an enthusiastic Medical Laboratory Officer in the making with great ambition and motivation to a transformative and professional Laboratory practices. Expert in organization and management with brilliant leadership skills with an aim of improving and providing quality services. Much interested in medical researches and discoveries of new methods for effective procedures and professionalism. Providing great quality services at skills in my disposal. I am also a self trained graphics and designer and have basic knowledge on website building.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Kenyatta University**

Bachelor's Degree in Medical Laboratory Science, 3rd Year.

#### **Enamel Computers Limited**

Certificate in Computer Packages

**Makueni Boys High School** Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education, 2018-2021

A-

#### **Kasunguni Primary School**

Kenya Certificate of Primary Education 2008-2017 394/500

## SKILLS

- Excellent computer operation skills
- Basic expertise in computer programming languages
- Graphic and designing skills
- Detail-oriented and able to handle multiple tasks simultaneously
- Performance of Laboratory tests and operation of modern laboratory equipment
- · Leadership skills and team building

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Certificate in Computer Packages
- ICT Co-Ordinator to a school research club (KUMESRES)

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### St Scholastica Uzima Hospital, Ruaraka Nairobi Laboratory Attachment | May, 2024-August, 2024

- Effectively worked in basic laboratory departments including phlebotomy, parasitology, microbiology and Biochemistry.
- Prepared and distributed lab reports for the patients
- Handled pediatric phlebotomy in the new born units
- Run tests using modern laboratory equipment at the facility
- Attended Medical camps in different areas around Nairobi as directed by the facility

#### AIC Zombe Mission Hospital, Zombe-Kitui

Laboratory Attachment | May, 2023-July, 2023

- Perfected on phlebotomy of patients
- Performed basic serological tests for the patients
- Assisted in the management of a clinic laboratory set up